https://www.ardsbookshop.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

We use cookies to make your experience better.
To comply with the new e-Privacy directive, we need to ask for your consent to set the cookies.
Learn more.
Allow Cookies
Menu
Home
BooksAdult Colouring BooksApologeticsApologeticsCreation and ScienceCults and the OccultEthics and Contemporary IssuesWorld ReligionsAudio BooksBiography and AutobiographyChristian LifeChurch and Bible HistoryBible History and BackgroundBible Texts and TranslationChurch HistoryHymnologyChurch and Pastoral ResourcesBereavementChurch Doctrine and PracticeChurch Prayer BooksCounsellingDiscipleshipEvangelism and MissionsForeign Language LiteratureGospel Tracts and BookletsLeadershipPastoral and Ministry HelpsPreaching Teaching and SermonsWorshipClassicsDevotional ReadingChristmas and Advent BooksDaily Readings and DevotionalsEaster and Lent BooksPoetryPrayerFictionHome and FamilyHome and FamilyMarriage and RelationshipsParentingMusic and Hymn BooksOther BooksGift BooksHealthLarge Print BooksPuzzle BooksProphecyReference and StudyAtlas Geography and ArcheologyBible Character BooksBible CommentariesBible Study ChartsBiblical LanguagesCollected SetsCommentaries by BookConcordancesDictionaries and EncyclopediasGeneral Bible StudyHandbook Introduction and SurveyHelps for New BelieversIndividual Group Bible StudiesPersonal Bible StudyTopical Bible StudiesTypology Temple and TabernacleTheologyHoly SpiritPerson and Work of ChristThe GodheadTheologyBiblesAudio BiblesKing James VersionKJV Compact and Slim BiblesKJV Economy and New TestamentsKJV Family and White BiblesKJV Large Print BiblesKJV Reference BiblesKJV Study BiblesKJV Wide Margin BiblesNew King James VersionNKJV Compact and Slim BiblesNKJV Economy and New TestamentsNKJV Large Print BiblesNKJV Reference BiblesNKJV Study BiblesEnglish Standard VersionESV Compact and Slim BiblesESV Economy and New TestamentsESV Journaling BiblesESV Large Print BiblesESV Reference BiblesESV Study BiblesESV Wide Margin BiblesNew International VersionNIV Compact and Slim BiblesNIV Economy and New TestamentsNIV Journaling BiblesNIV Large Print BiblesNIV Reference BiblesNIV Study BiblesNIV Text BiblesNew Living TranslationNLT Compact and Slim BiblesNLT Economy and New TestamentsNLT Large Print BiblesNLT Reference BiblesNLT Study BiblesAmplified BibleDarby BibleForeign Language BiblesGood News BibleChristian Standard BibleHolman Christian Standard BibleInterlinear BiblesMessage BibleNET Bible TranslationNew American Standard BibleNew Century VersionNew Revised Standard VersionOther Bible TranslationsParallel BiblesRevised Standard VersionMusicTraditional MusicSouthern Gospel MusicPraise and Worship MusicContemporary MusicInstrumental MusicChristmas MusicDVDDocumentary DVDFeature Film DVDSouthern Gospel Music DVDTeaching and Group Study DVDTraditional Music DVDWorship Contemporary DVDKidsKids BiblesBaby Gift BiblesESV Kids BiblesICB NCV Kids BiblesKJV Kids BiblesNIV Kids BiblesNKJV Kids BiblesNLT Kids BiblesOther Kids BiblesKids Board GamesKids BooksKids Bible HelpsKids Bible StoriesKids BiographyKids Board BooksKids Books on CDKids Books on PrayerKids Christian LifeKids Christmas BooksKids ClassicsKids Colour Puzzle BooksKids DevotionalKids Easter BooksKids FictionKids Gift BooksKids Story BiblesKids Music and DVDKids Animated DVDKids Feature DVDKids MusicKids Music DVDKids Teaching DVDKids Picture TextsKids ResourcesKids and Youth EvangelismKids Youth Ministry ResourcesYouthYouth BiblesESV Youth BiblesHCSB Youth BiblesKJV Youth BiblesNCV Youth BiblesNIV Youth BiblesNKJV Youth BiblesNLT Youth BiblesOther Youth BiblesYouth BooksYouth Bible StudyYouth BiographyYouth Christian LifeYouth DevotionalYouth FictionYouth Group Individual StudyYouth Teaching and GuidancePreorderGift tokensAbout usWelcome to AEBLocation & hoursCataloguesShipping and returnsCommunity events
AEB blog
New titles Personal reflections Events Recommended reading Thoughts on Scripture
Account
Home
Privacy and Cookie Policy
Privacy and Cookie Policy
This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you provide while using this website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Our privacy guarantee
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by letting us know using our Contact Us information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties other than for the purposes of shipping. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
Payments through ardsbookshop.com are processed securely by a payment processing company and we do not receive your card details. If you place an order via telephone, we will take you card details. We do not archive your card details and only store them while the order is active, after which time they are shredded. They are not stored on computer for security reasons.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us this request using our Contact Us information.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
Cookie Name
Cookie Description
FORM_KEY
Stores randomly generated key used to prevent forged requests.
PHPSESSID
Your session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to view and edit their orders.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history, if you have asked for this.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
MAGE-CACHE-SESSID
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-STORAGE-SECTION-INVALIDATION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
MAGE-CACHE-TIMEOUT
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
SECTION-DATA-IDS
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
PRIVATE_CONTENT_VERSION
Facilitates caching of content on the browser to make pages load faster.
X-MAGENTO-VARY
Facilitates caching of content on the server to make pages load faster.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-FILE-VERSION
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAGE-TRANSLATION-STORAGE
Facilitates translation of content to other languages.
MAILCHIMP_CAMPAIGN_ID
Facilitates subscription to the AEB newsletter.
MAILCHIMP_LANDING_PAGE
Facilitates subscription to the AEB newsletter.
MCPOPUPCLOSED
Facilitates subscription to the AEB newsletter.
Free postage
Orders over £10 qualify for free postage within the UK.
We are here to help
Can't find what you are looking for?Give us a call on 02891817530.
Payment methods
We accept payment by cheque, credit card and PayPal.
Information
Search TermsPrivacy and Cookie PolicyAdvanced SearchOrders and ReturnsContact UsRSS
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
Copyright © 2020 Ards Evangelical Bookshop. All rights reserved.
Top
